<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="enable_pin_code">Enable PIN code</string>
    <string name="enable_pin_code_to_better_secure">Enable PIN code in settings to better secure your wallet.</string>
    <string name="old_android_warning">Your device is using an old version of Android that is less secure. Switch to a device with a more recent Android version for better security.</string>
    <string name="write_down_backup_passphrase_suggestion">Write down or memorize your 12 word wallet backup passphrase which can be found in settings. Your wallet backup passphrase is needed to recover your bitcoins.</string>
    <string name="display_local_currency">Display local Currency</string>
    <string name="enable_dynamic_fee">Enable Dynamic Fee</string>
    <string name="fixed_fee_amount">Set Fixed Fee Amount</string>
    <string name="dynamic_fee_options">Select Dynamic Fee Option</string>
    <string name="backup_passphrase_colon">Backup Passphrase:</string>
    <string name="mnemonic">Mnemonic</string>
    <string name="account_public_key">Account Public Key</string>
    <string name="account_public_key_colon">Account Public Key:</string>
    <string name="account_private_key">Account Private Key</string>
    <string name="account_private_key_colon">Account Private Key:</string>
    <string name="show_backup_passphrase">Show Backup Passphrase</string>
    <string name="restore_wallet">Restore Wallet</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="advanced_settings">Advanced Settings</string>
    <string name="enable_advanced_mode">Enable advanced mode</string>
    <string name="enable_cold_wallet">Enable cold wallet</string>
    <string name="default_reusable_addresses">Default Reusable Addresses</string>
    <string name="block_explorer_api">Block Explorer API</string>
    <string name="block_explorer_api_type">Block Explorer API type</string>
    <string name="block_explorer_url">Block Explorer URL</string>
    <string name="set_transaction_fee_in">Set Transaction Fee in %1$s</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="private_key_does_not_match_address">Private key does not match address</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="like_using_arcbit">Like using ArcBit?</string>
    <string name="checkout_the_arcbit_web_wallet">Check out the ArcBit Web Wallet!</string>
    <string name="checkout_the_arcbit_web_wallet_description">Use ArcBit on your browser to complement the mobile app. The web wallet has all the features that the mobile wallet has plus more!</string>
    <string name="error_fetching_unspent_outputs_try_again">Error fetching unspent outputs. Try again.</string>
    <string name="error_fetching_unspent_outputs_try_again_later">Error fetching unspent outputs. Try again later.</string>
    <string name="unable_to_get_dynamic_fees">Unable to get dynamic fees. Falling back on fixed transaction fee. (fee can be configured on review payment)</string>
    <string name="cold_wallet_private_keys_not_store_here">Cold wallet private keys are not stored here and cannot be viewed.</string>
    <string name="invalid_account_private_key">Invalid account private key</string>
    <string name="more_funds_needed">You have %1$s, but %2$s is needed.advanced_settings (This includes the transactions fee)</string>
    <string name="account_private_key_not_match_imported_account_public_key">Account private key does not match imported account public key</string>
    <string name="invalid_uri_does_not_contain__address">Invalid Bitcoin URI, does not contain an address.</string>
    <string name="send_to_reusable_address_warning">You are making a payment to a reusable address. Make sure that the receiver can see the payment made to them. (All ArcBit reusable addresses are compatible with other ArcBit wallets)</string>
    <string name="send_to_reusable_address_not_insight">Sending payment to a reusable address might take longer to show up then a normal transaction with the blockchain.info API. You might have to wait until at least 1 confirmation for the transaction to show up. This is due to the limitations of the blockchain.info API. For reusable address payments to show up faster, configure your app to use the Insight API in advance settings.</string>
    <string name="too_high_fee">Your new transaction fee is too high</string>
    <string name="sent_amount_to_address">Sent %1$s to %2$s</string>
    <string name="funds_may_be_pending_confirmation">Some funds may be pending confirmation and cannot be spent yet. (Check your account history) Account only has a spendable balance of %1$s</string>
    <string name="insufficient_funds_dust">Insufficient Funds. Account contains bitcoin dust. You can only send up to %1$s for now.</string>
    <string name="cannot_create_transactions_with_outputs_less_then">Cannot create transactions with outputs less then %1$s</string>
    <string name="insufficient_funds_account_balance">"Insufficient Funds. Account balance is %1$s when %2$s is required."</string>
    <string name="imported_watch_addresses">Imported Watch Addresses</string>
    <string name="cold_wallet_accounts">Cold Wallet Accounts</string>
    <string name="imported_watch_accounts">Imported Watch Accounts</string>
    <string name="imported_accounts">Imported Accounts</string>
    <string name="select_account">Select Account</string>
    <string name="invalid_backup_passphrase">Invalid backup passphrase</string>
    <string name="restoring_wallet">Restoring Wallet</string>
    <string name="restor_wallet_explanation">Your current wallet will be deleted. Your can restore your current wallet later with the wallet passphrase, but any imported accounts or addresses created in advanced mode cannot be recovered. Do you wish to continue?</string>
    <string name="your_wallet_is_now_restored">Your wallet is now restored</string>
    <string name="receive">Receive</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="start_using_the_app_now">Welcome to ArcBit, a user only controlled Bitcoin wallet. Start using the app now by depositing your bitcoins here.</string>
    <string name="ask_to_restore_wallet">Do you want to restore from your backup passphrase or start a new wallet?</string>
    <string name="backup_passphrase_found">Backup passphrase found in keychain</string>
    <string name="passphrase_instructions">Write down the 12 word passphrase below and keep it safe. You can restore your entire wallets\' bitcoins with this single passphrase. The passphrase is also known as the seed or mnemonic.</string>
    <string name="passphrase_instructions_advanced">"Write down the 12 word passphrase below and keep it safe. You can restore your entire wallets\' bitcoins (excluding imports) with this single passphrase. The passphrase is also known as the seed or mnemonic.</string>
    <string name="master_seed_hex_description">The master seed hex is derived from the passphrase. If you want to import Bitcoins into another wallet, and if that other wallets don\'t use BIP39, then it\'s possible to import the Bitcoins using the master seed hex as long as they support BIP44.</string>
    <string name="master_seed_hex">Master Seed Hex</string>
    <string name="wallet_backup_passphrase">Wallet backup passphrase</string>
    <string name="passphrase">Passphrase</string>
    <string name="restore_wallet_description">Enter a wallet backup passphrase to wipe the current wallet and start/restore another.</string>
    <string name="review_payment">Review Payment</string>
    <string name="contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="accounts">Accounts</string>
    <string name="cold_wallet">Cold Wallet</string>

    <string name="cold_wallet_overview">Cold Wallet Overview</string>
    <string name="authorize_payment">Authorize Payment</string>
    <string name="create_cold_wallet">Create Cold Wallet</string>
    <string name="authorize_cold_wallet_account_payment">Authorize Cold Wallet Account Payment</string>
    <string name="internal_wallet_data">Internal Wallet Data</string>
    <string name="cold_wallet_overview_description">The cold wallet feature will allow you to create accounts which offer better security then normal online wallets. You will need 2 devices to use this feature. Your normal day to day device that is connected to the internet and a secondary device that is not connected to the internet (Your secondary device would need to be online once to download the ArcBit app. Afterwards keep the secondary device offline for maximal security). This feature allows you to authorize bitcoin payments from an offline device so that the keys to your bitcoins will never need to be store on your online device. Follow the step by step instructions by clicking the info buttons within the below sections.</string>
    <string name="create_cold_wallet_mnemonic_description">First make sure you are using your secondary offline device for this screen (as mentioned in the overview in the previous screen). Click \'New Wallet\' and write down or memorized the generated 12 word passphrase. This passphrase can recover and generate all your accounts and the bitcoins associated with it, so keep it safe and to yourself. Also instead of creating a new wallet, you can also input an existing 12 word passphrase that was generated here to create additional accounts.</string>
    <string name="create_cold_wallet_account_description">Input an account ID and click \'QR Code\'. Then on your primary online device, enable Cold Wallet in settings. Then go to the accounts screen and click \'Import Cold Wallet Account\' and scan the Account Public Key QR Code. Afterwards use this cold wallet account as you would a normal account and deposits bitcoins into it. When you want to make a payment from a cold wallet account, go to the next section in the previous screen and follow the step by step instructions there.</string>
    <string name="brain_wallet">Brain Wallet</string>
    <string name="address_id_colon_number">Address ID %1$d:</string>
    <string name="change_address_id_colon_number">Change Address ID %1$d:</string>

    <string name="step_1_scan_transaction_to_authorize">Step 1: Scan transaction to authorize</string>
    <string name="step_2_input_12_word_backup_passphrase">Step 2: Input 12 word backup passphrase</string>
    <string name="step_3_pass_authorized_transaction_data">Step 3: Pass authorized transaction data</string>
    <string name="scan_transaction_to_authorize_info">On your primary online device, when you want to make a payment from a cold wallet account, simply do it as would normally would on a normal account. When you click \'Send\' on the Review Payment screen, instead of the payment going out immediately, you will be prompt to pass the unauthorized transaction data. Then on your secondary offline device, within this screen click \'Scan\' to import the transaction so it can be authorized.</string>
    <string name="input_12_word_backup_passphrase_info">Input the 12 word passphrase/mnemonic that belongs to the cold wallet account that you want to make a payment from. This is the passphrase that was used to generate your account public key that was generated in the \'Create Cold Wallet\' section found in the previous screen.</string>
    <string name="pass_authorized_transaction_data_info">Once the transaction has been authorized by completing the above two steps, pass the authorized transaction back to your primary online device to finalize your payment.</string>
    <string name="incomplete">Incomplete</string>
    <string name="complete">Complete</string>
    <string name="invalid_scanned_data">Invalid scanned data</string>
    <string name="x_over_y_complete">%1$d/%2$d Complete</string>
    <string name="transaction_authorized">Transaction authorized</string>
    <string name="transaction_authorized_next_step_description">Transaction needs to be passed back to your online device in order for the payment to be sent</string>
    <string name="complete_step_1">Complete step 1</string>
    <string name="passphrase_does_not_match_the_transaction">Passphrase does not match the transaction</string>


    <string name="unconfirmed">Unconfirmed</string>
    <string name="one_confirmation">1 Confirmation</string>
    <string name="internal_account_transfer">Internal account transfer</string>
    <string name="view_in_web">View in web</string>
    <string name="label_transaction">Label Transaction</string>
    <string name="copy_transaction_id_to_clipboard">Copy Transaction ID to Clipboard</string>
    <string name="edit_transaction_label">Edit Transaction label</string>
    <string name="import_with_qr_code">Import with QR code</string>
    <string name="import_with_text_input">Import with text input</string>
    <string name="new_address_generation_explanation">New addresses will be automatically generated and cycled for you as you use your current available addresses.</string>
    <string name="reusable_address_watch_only_account_explanation">Imported Watch Only Accounts can\'t see reusable address payments, thus this accounts\' reusable address is not available. If you want see the reusable address for this account import the account private key that corresponds to this accounts public key.</string>
    <string name="reusable_address_cold_wallet_account_explanation">Cold Wallet Accounts can\'t see reusable address payments, thus this accounts\' reusable address is not available.</string>
    <string name="edit_contact_name">Edit Contact Name</string>
    <string name="delete_contact">Delete contact?</string>
    <string name="input_address">Input address</string>
    <string name="input_contact_name_for_address">Input contact name for address</string>
    <string name="add_non_reusable_address_to_contacts_warning">It is not recommended that you use a regular bitcoin address for multiple payments, but instead you should import a reusable address. Add address anyways?</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="email_support">Email Support</string>
    <string name="arcbit_web_wallet">Arcbit Web Wallet</string>
    <string name="arcbit_ios_wallet">Arcbit iOS Wallet</string>
    <string name="arcbit_brain_wallet">Arcbit Brain Wallet</string>
    <string name="check_out_the_arcbit_web_wallet">Check out the ArcBit Web Wallet</string>
    <string name="check_out_the_arcbit_ios_wallet">Check out the ArcBit iOS Wallet</string>
    <string name="check_out_the_arcbit_brain_wallet">Check out the ArcBit Brain Wallet</string>
    <string name="view_arcbit_web_wallet_details">View ArcBit Web Wallet Details</string>
    <string name="view_arcbit_brain_wallet_details">View ArcBit Brain Wallet Details</string>
    <string name="other_links">Other Links</string>
    <string name="follow_us_on_twitter">Follow us on Twitter</string>
    <string name="dear_arcbit_support">Dear ArcBit Support,</string>
    <string name="android_support">Android Support</string>
    <string name="arcbit_brain_wallet_detail">\tWith the Arcbit Brain Wallet you can safely spend your bitcoins without ever having your private keys be exposed to the internet. It can be use in conjuction with your Arcbit Wallet or as a stand alone wallet.\n</string>
    <string name="arcbit_web_wallet_detail">\tArcBit Web Wallet is a Chrome extension. It has all the features of the mobile wallet plus more. Highlights include the ability to create multiple wallets instead of just one, and a new non-cumbersome way to generate wallets, store and spend bitcoins all from cold storage! ArcBit\'s new way to manage your cold storage bitcoins also offers a more compelling reason to use ArcBit\'s watch only account feature. Now you can safely watch the balance of your cold storage bitcoins by enabling advance mode in ArcBit and importing your cold storage account public keys.\n</string>
    <string name="arcbit_web_wallet_detail_2">\tUse ArcBit Web Wallet in whatever way you wish. You can create a new wallet, or you can input your current 12 word backup passphrase to manage the same bitcoins across different devices. Check out the ArcBit Web Wallet in the Chrome Web Store for more details.\n</string>
    <string name="enable_advanced_mode_description">Enabling advanced mode will expose hidden features, including the ability to import bitcoin private keys and addresses. Please note that the backup passphrase cannot recover your bitcoin private keys and addresses, so they should be backed up separately. To see a list of all the advance features, enable advanced mode and go to the Help section.</string>
    <string name="enable_cold_wallet_description">Enabling the cold wallet feature will allow you to create accounts which offer better security then normal online wallets. You will need 2 devices to use this feature. Your normal day to day device that is connected to the internet and another device that is not connected to the internet. You can find the cold wallet feature on the side menu.</string>
    <string name="enable_default_reusable_address_description">Enabling reusable addresses as default will put all account reusable addresses in the front of the receiving address list in the Receive Screen.</string>
    <string name="enable_recoverable_description">This feature allows you to recover your native ArcBit wallet if you delete this app. Your backup passphrase is stored in your keychain and if you enable this feature a re-installed app will be able to read it. This feature does not allow recovery of wallets or addresses which you imported into other accounts.</string>
    <string name="exit_app_to_take_effect">You must exit and kill this app in order for this to take effect.</string>
    <string name="change_block_explorer_url">Change block explorer URL</string>
    <string name="cannot_select_custom_url_for_this_block_explorer">Cannot select custom URL for this block explorer</string>
    <string name="none_currently">None currently</string>
    <string name="this_account_type_cant_see_reusable_address_payments">This account type can\'t see reusable address payments</string>
    <string name="reusable_address_colon">Reusable Address: %1$s</string>
    <string name="reusable_address_payment_addresses">Reusable Address Payment Addresses</string>
    <string name="active_main_addresses">Active Main Addresses</string>
    <string name="archived_main_addresses">Archived Main Addresses</string>
    <string name="active_change_addresses">Active Change Addresses</string>
    <string name="archived_change_addresses">Archived Change Addresses</string>
    <string name="payment_index_colon">Payment Index:</string>
    <string name="starting_receiving_address_id_colon">Starting Receiving Address ID:</string>
    <string name="address_id_colon">Address ID:</string>
    <string name="qr_code">QR code</string>
    <string name="view_address_qr_code">View address QR code</string>
    <string name="view_private_key_qr_code">View private key QR code</string>
    <string name="qr_code_address_warning">Do not use the QR code from here to receive bitcoins. Go to the Receive screen to get a QR code to receive bitcoins.</string>
    <string name="qr_code_key_warning">It is not recommended that you manually manage private keys yourself. A leak of a private key can lead to the compromise of your accounts\' bitcoins.</string>
    <string name="account_private_key_missing">Account private key missing</string>
    <string name="ask_import_your_account_private_key">Do you want to temporary import your account private key?</string>
    <string name="private_key_missing">Private key missing</string>
    <string name="ask_import_your_private_key">Do you want to temporary import your private key?</string>
    <string name="import_private_key">Import private key</string>
    <string name="temporary_import_private_key">Temporary import private key</string>
    <string name="temporary_import_account_private_key">Temporary import account private key</string>
    <string name="invalid_passphrase">Invalid Passphrase</string>
    <string name="enter_password_for_encrypted_private_key">Enter password for encrypted private key</string>
    <string name="archived_accounts">Archived Accounts</string>
    <string name="archived_cold_wallet_accounts">Archived Cold Wallet Accounts</string>
    <string name="archived_imported_accounts">Archived Imported Accounts</string>
    <string name="archived_imported_watch_accounts">Archived Imported Watch Accounts</string>
    <string name="archived_imported_addresses">Archived Imported Addresses</string>
    <string name="archived_imported_watch_addresses">Archived Imported Watch Addresses</string>
    <string name="actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="import_cold_wallet_account">Import Cold Wallet Account</string>
    <string name="import_account">Import Account</string>
    <string name="import_watch_only_account">Import Watch Only Account</string>
    <string name="import_watch_only_address">Import Watch Only Address</string>
    <string name="created_new_account">Created new account</string>
    <string name="account_number">Account %1$d</string>
    <string name="view_account_public_key_qr_code">View account public key QR code</string>
    <string name="view_account_private_key_qr_code">View account private key QR code</string>
    <string name="view_addresses">View Addresses</string>
    <string name="edit_account_name">Edit Account Name</string>
    <string name="unarchive_account">Unarchive Account</string>
    <string name="account_id_colon">Account ID:</string>
    <string name="change_address_id_colon">Change address ID:</string>
    <string name="account_id_number">Account ID: %1$d</string>
    <string name="archive_account">Archive Account</string>
    <string name="rename_account">Rename Account</string>
    <string name="clear_account_private_key_from_memory">Clear account private key from memory</string>
    <string name="clear_private_key_from_memory">Clear private key from memory</string>
    <string name="cleared_from_memory">Cleared from memory</string>
    <string name="view_address_in_web">View address in web</string>
    <string name="archive_address">Archive address</string>
    <string name="enter_label">Enter Label</string>
    <string name="unarchived_address">Unarchived address</string>
    <string name="delete_address">Delete address</string>
    <string name="maximum_accounts_reached">Maximum accounts reached</string>
    <string name="maximum_accounts_reached_need_to_archive">You need to archived an account in order to unarchive a different one.</string>
    <string name="scan_for_reusable_address_transaction">Scan for reusable address transaction</string>
    <string name="transaction_id">Transaction ID</string>
    <string name="transaction_is_not_a_reusable_address_transaction">Transaction is not a reusable address transaction.</string>
    <string name="funds_have_been_claimed_already">Funds have been claimed already.</string>
    <string name="funds_imported">Funds imported</string>
    <string name="transaction_does_not_belong_to_account">Transaction %1$s does not belong to this account.</string>
    <string name="transaction_already_accounted_for">Transaction %1$s already accounted for.</string>
    <string name="checking_transaction">Checking Transaction</string>
    <string name="error_fetching_transaction">Error fetching Transaction</string>
    <string name="scan_payment_txid_description">This feature allows you to manually input a transaction id and see if the corresponding transaction contains a forwarding payment to your reusable address. If so, then the funds will be added to your wallet. Normally the app will discover forwarding payments automatically for you, but if you believe a payment is missing you can use this feature.</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_unarchive_account">Are you sure you want to unarchive account %1$s?</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_archive_account">Are you sure you want to archive account %1$s?</string>
    <string name="cannot_archive_your_default_account">Cannot archive your default account</string>
    <string name="cannot_archive_your_one_and_only_account">Cannot archive your one and only account</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_archive_address">Are you sure you want to archive address %1$s?</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_unarchive_address">Are you sure you want to unarchive address %1$s?</string>
    <string name="unarchive_address">Unarchive address</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_delete_this_account">Are you sure you want to delete this account?</string>
    <string name="account_account_name_imported">Account %1$s imported</string>
    <string name="error_importing_account">Error importing account</string>
    <string name="importing_account">Importing Account</string>
    <string name="importing_cold_wallet_account_account_name">Imported Cold Wallet Account %1$s</string>
    <string name="imported_account_account_name">Imported Account %1$s</string>
    <string name="importing_watch_account_account_name">Imported Watch Account %1$s</string>
    <string name="importing_cold_wallet_account">Importing Cold Wallet Account</string>
    <string name="importing_watch_account">Importing Watch Account</string>
    <string name="invalid_account_public_key">Invalid account public key</string>
    <string name="encrypted">encrypted</string>
    <string name="unencrypted">unencrypted</string>
    <string name="decrypting">Decrypting</string>
    <string name="cannot_import_reusable_address">Cannot import reusable address</string>
    <string name="input_account_private_key">Input account private key</string>
    <string name="input_account_public_key">Input account public key</string>
    <string name="scan_for_reusable_address_payment">Scan For Reusable Address Payment</string>
    <string name="import_private_key_encrypted_or_unencrypted">Import private key encrypted or unencrypted?</string>
    <string name="import_private_key_encrypted_or_unencrypted_description">Importing key encrypted will require you to input the password everytime you want to send bitcoins from it.</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="app_name">ArcBit</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="fee_adjusted_to_confirm">Fee adjusted to confirm...</string>
    <string name="hd_accounts">Accounts</string>
    <string name="invalid_url">Invalid URL</string>
    <string name="create_new_account">Create new Account</string>
    <string name="pass">Pass</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="delete_account_name">Delete %1$s</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="address_colon">Address: %1$s</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="invalid_transaction_id">Invalid transaction ID</string>
    <string name="transaction_fee_how">Transaction fees impact how quickly the Bitcoin mining network will confirm your transactions, and depend on the current network conditions.</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="from_colon">From:</string>
    <string name="from">From</string>
    <string name="to_colon">To:</string>
    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="amount_colon">Amount:</string>
    <string name="amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="device_rooted_description">Your device appears to be rooted. Be advised that storing funds on a rooted device is unsafe and, in addition, can cause stability issues.</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection_description">Cannot obtain an Internet connection. Please check the connectivity on your device and try again.</string>
    <string name="account_received_amount">%1$s received %2$s</string>
    <string name="amount_confirmations">%1$s Confirmations</string>
    <string name="id_colon">ID: %1$s</string>
    <string name="create_new_contact">Create new contact</string>
    <string name="bitcoin_unit">Bitcoin Unit</string>
    <string name="local_currency">Local Currency</string>
    <string name="ok_capitalize">OK</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate us in the Play Store!</string>
    <string name="continue_capitalize">Continue</string>
    <string name="remind_me_later">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="dont_remind_me">Don\'t remind me</string>
    <string name="back_up_wallet">Back up wallet</string>
    <string name="sending">Sending...</string>
    <string name="disable_pin">Disable PIN</string>
    <string name="enter_new_pin">Enter new PIN</string>
    <string name="reenter_new_pin">Reenter new PIN</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="edit_label">Edit label</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="label">Label</string>
    <string name="scan_qr">Scan QR Code</string>
    <string name="new_wallet">New Wallet</string>
    <string name="imported_addresses">Imported Addresses</string>
    <string name="imported_address">Imported Address</string>
    <string name="import_address">Import Address</string>
    <string name="invalid_private_key">Invalid private key</string>
    <string name="invalid_bitcoin_address">Invalid Bitcoin address</string>
    <string name="invalid_amount">Invalid amount</string>
    <string name="insufficient_funds">Insufficient funds</string>
    <string name="not_now">Not now</string>
    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="high_fee_not_necessary">High fee not necessary.</string>
    <string name="low_fee_not_recommended">Low Custom Fee Not Recommended</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="invalid_pin">Invalid PIN. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="pin_mismatch_error">PINs do not match</string>
    <string name="create_pin">Create PIN</string>
    <string name="confirm_pin">Confirm PIN</string>
    <string name="change_pin_code">Change PIN</string>
    <string name="enter_current_pin">Please enter current PIN.</string>
    <string name="pin_entry">Enter PIN</string>
    <string name="copied_to_clipboard">Copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="send_payment">Send Payment</string>
    <string name="transaction_fee">Transaction Fee</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Drawer open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Drawer close</string>
    <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="request_camera_permission">Camera access is required.</string>
    <string name="fee">Fee</string>
    <string name="customize">customize</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="screen_overlay_detected">Screen overlay detected!</string>
    <string name="screen_overlay_description">Apps that use screen overlays have the ability to trick you
        into tapping on unseen objects and potentially steal funds. Note that this warning will also be triggered by screen dimming apps. If you are confident that there
        is no threat you may continue.
    </string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="camera_unavailable">The camera is currently opened by another application. Please close other application and try again.</string>
    <string name="addresses">Addresses</string>
    <string name="select_units">Select BTC units</string>
    <string name="select_currency">Select Currency</string>
    <string name="cannot_use_app_on_this_device">ArcBit Wallet cannot be run on this device.</string>
    <string name="backup_wallet">backup wallet</string>

    <string name="parts_scanned">%1$d/%2$d parts scanned.</string>
    <string name="scan_next_part">Scan next part</string>
    <string name="send_authorized_payment">Send authorized payment?</string>
    <string name="finished_passing_transaction_data">Finished Passing Transaction Data</string>
    <string name="finished_passing_transaction_data_description">Now authorize the transaction on your air gap device. When you have done so click continue on this device to scan the authorized transaction data and make your payment.</string>
    <string name="spending_from_a_cold_wallet_account">Spending from a cold wallet account</string>
    <string name="spending_from_a_cold_wallet_account_description">Transaction needs to be authorize by an offline and airgap device. Send transaction to an offline device for authorization?</string>
    <string name="try_our_new_cold_wallet_feature">Try our new cold wallet feature!</string>
    <string name="try_our_new_cold_wallet_feature_description">With an ArcBit cold wallet feature, you can create wallets and make payments offline without exposing your private keys to an internet connected device. This feature is great for storing large amounts of bitcoins or for the security conscious minded. Check out this feature in the cold wallet section in the side menu.</string>
</resources>